metrolist.com 2019-05-14

# Privacy Policy | iHomefinder

### iHomefinder, Inc. Privacy Policy

Your privacy is very important to iHomefinder. iHomefinder treats all personal information about you with great respect and takes various measures to protect your privacy and to secure all information about you.

When you visit our website(s) and use various aspects of our IDX Programs, Features and Services, we collect information such as the web browser you are using, your Internet Protocol (IP) address, visit date and time, and referring website. You may visit our website(s) and use various aspects of our IDX Programs, Features, and Services without revealing any additional information. Other aspects of our IDX Programs, Features, Services, and our website(s) may allow you to provide us with personal information so that you can receive MLS® System data and additional information or customer support from iHomefinder.

All personal information that you voluntarily submit or enter into the iHomefinder system is kept confidential and is used solely by iHomefinder and third parties working on our behalf and bound by our confidentiality agreements. Neither iHomefinder nor any of our third party vendors will release any of your personal information to any other party unless you expressly permit it or if we are required to do so by law, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims.

iHomefinder's website and programs and/or our clients' websites and third party vendors may provide various features, tools, and links to other websites. Any such features, tools and/or linked websites are not bound by our privacy policy, and iHomefinder cannot assume any responsibility for any of the information gathered when you use or access any of these features, tools or linked websites.

Please read the details below to learn more about our privacy policy. iHomefinder reserves the right to modify this Privacy Policy from time to time.

### Information Collection and Use

iHomefinder collects personal information when you sign up for an account with iHomefinder, when you use various aspects of our IDX Programs, Features and Services, and when you visit our website(s). When you sign up for an account with iHomefinder, we will collect information including, but not limited to, name, address, phone number, email address, and billing information. Once you sign-up for an account with us, you establish a relationship with us and authorize us to collect, record and make use of your personal information in order to provide with MLS® System data and related services.

When you use our IDX Programs, Features and Services, and/or our website, we automatically receive and record information on our server logs such as the web browser you are using, your Internet Protocol (IP) address, visit date and time, and referring website. We may also ask for contact information including, but not limited to, name, email address, and phone number. We also collect information on your use of our products so that we may provide the information you request and so that we may improve our products and business practices, contact you, conduct research, and provide reports for our clients. This information may also be utilized for marketing purposes, and to assess trends in lead capture for your account and for broker office statistics. iHomefinder may combine information about you that we have with information we obtain from business partners, including but not limited to our resellers, affiliated website designers and customer support providers, marketing and customer relationship management ("CRM") partners, or other companies.

We also collect and use information pursuant to our Cookies policy, below.

### Data Retention

iHomefinder will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. We will also retain personal data we process on behalf of our clients for as long as needed to provide services to our client. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

You may request to review, correct, delete or otherwise modify any of the personal information that you have previously provided to us. If you have registered for an account, you may log in and update your user settings. You can also update the contact details of your leads at any time. Otherwise, to access, correct, delete your personal information, please contact us as specified below and we will respond to your request within a reasonable timeframe.

### Information Sharing and Disclosure

iHomefinder does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you, or any data collected via your iHomefinder account, with other people or nonaffiliated companies except to provide MLS® System Data, Products Features or Services you've requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances:

We provide the information to our partners, including but not limited to office administrators, designer of the website you use, or to the real estate board/MLS® System provider to which you or your agent belong, or any other third party who works on your behalf with an express written agreement, or with iHomefinder under our own confidentiality agreements. Our partners and service providers do not have any independent right to share this information.

When you visit our website and provide information such as name, email address, and phone number, we in turn provide this information to marketing and CRM partners, so we may follow up with you, utilizing software or services from our partners, to give you more information about our IDX Programs, Features, and Services.

iHomefinder will respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims.

iHomefinder will share necessary information in order to investigate or take action regarding suspected illegal activities, situations involving potential threats to the safety of any person, violations of iHomefinder's License Agreement, Terms of Use, DMCA Notice, or as otherwise required by law.

iHomefinder will transfer information about you if iHomefinder is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, iHomefinder will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

We also share and disclose information pursuant to our Cookies policy, below.

### Cookies

iHomefinder sets cookies in your browser when you visit our company website, www.ihomefinder.com, and the websites of our clients using our products and services, in order to record aspects of your website visit and to provide you with various data and related services. Our company website uses tracking features from providers including Google AdSense, Google AdWords, and Bing Ads that set a cookie in your browser when you visit our website or click on one of our ads, to record web activity and serve iHomefinder ads to you on other websites across the internet. We also use these Google Analytics features to collect data about web traffic via non-personally identifiable information: Remarketing with Google Analytics, Google Display Network Impression Reporting, DoubleClick Platform integrations, and Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting. Our IDX search tools on client websites use features, via non-personally identifiable information, including lead source tracking (to note the referring marketing campaign for a site visit), and clickstream data analysis (to note consumer patterns in visiting IDX content). When required by a local real estate board or MLS® System, iHomefinder IDX pages can include cookies for ListTrac visit data tools, which may be aggregated with metadata from many IDX websites into analytics reports and advertising profile information, per local real estate board or MLS® System policies and practices.

Third-party vendors, including Google, also use cookies to serve iHomefinder ads across the internet, based on your past visits to [www.ihomefinder.com](https://www.ihomefinder.com/). You can opt out of Google's use of cookies by visiting [Google's Ads Settings](http://www.google.com/settings/ads). You can opt out of Bing's use of cookies by visiting [Microsoft personalized ad preferences](https://choice.microsoft.com/en-us/opt-out). You can opt out of Google Analytics by visiting the [Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on page](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/). You can opt out of a third-party vendor's use of cookies by visiting the [Network Advertising Initiative opt-out page](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp). You can opt out of cookies in your browser by using the settings specific to your browser. By opting out of cookies, some IDX Programs, Features, and Services might not function fully or correctly, and iHomefinder ads might not display on other websites you visit.

### Canada Anti-Spam Law (CASL) Notice

Please note, if you are in Canada, by providing an email address on our website(s), display ads, or in our IDX Programs, Features, and Services, you provide express consent to receive emails from iHomefinder or from iHomefinder clients who are using our IDX Programs, Features, and Services.

### Changes to this Privacy Policy

iHomefinder reserves the right to update this policy from time to time. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your iHomefinder account or by placing a prominent notice on our site.

### Questions and Suggestions

If you have questions or suggestions, you can [contact us](https://www.ihomefinder.com/contact-us/).
